[["Listen, Walter --", {"entities": [[8, 14, "PERSON"]]}],
["Austin Powers? Hi, I'm Andy Warhol.", {"entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [23, 34, "PERSON"]]}],
["Silicone Valley. Lots of these science guys never leave that place. We book two shows a month in there. Those big time techs and bio- guys might be real high zoners up here, but when it comes to the arts, they like it loud and lewd.", {"entities": [[86, 93, "TIME"], [0, 15, "GPE"]]}],
["Well, you're doing something wrong, Mrs. Sutphin. I'd recommend therapy for your son. Thank you for taking the time to come to PTA.", {"entities": [[41, 48, "PERSON"], [127, 130, "ORG"]]}],
["I want you to take this, Lenny. Today's your day of atonement. I know how guilty you feel about that woman and her baby --", {"entities": [[32, 37, "DATE"], [25, 30, "PERSON"]]}],
["I've been overseeing production myself for the past three years, you'll be surprised at how wonderful our oil has become.", {"entities": [[47, 63, "TIME"]]}],
["White House Situation room.", {"entities": [[0, 11, "ORG"]]}],
["Keep it anyway. I have another one at home.", {"entities": [[38, 42, "LOC"]]}],
["I didn't say that. Growing up in an orphanage, you're always lonely. You're just never alone.", {"entities": [[36, 45, "LOC"]]}],
["Leif, you sit there. Even, you sit there. Harald, you'd better sit over there...", {"entities": [[42, 48, "PERSON"], [0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Can't that wait, Hubert?", {"entities": [[17, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
["And if we don't invite Maranzano, we can't invite Masseria. Guys don't wanna be choosin' sides.", {"entities": [[50, 58, "PERSON"], [23, 32, "PERSON"]]}],
["Commander, you and Lt. Madison will have to go through the crushers one at a time in three second intervals. Tell me when the first crusher hits the bottom...", {"entities": [[19, 30, "PERSON"], [82, 97, "TIME"]]}],
["Valo massa... Chacha hamas.", {"entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"]]}],
["I got my things over at the hotel. I'll bring them over later... Come here.", {"entities": [[28, 33, "LOC"]]}],
["She washes hair up at Ludwig's - a salon on 63rd and Madison.", {"entities": [[22, 28, "ORG"], [35, 40, "LOC"], [53, 60, "GPE"]]}],
["Then who?! Because someone wants another blood harvest. With human blood, Jeremiah! Just like Jethro! Who did he kill back then, Jeremiah? Farmhands? Transients? People no one would miss? ", {"entities": [[94, 100, "ORG"], [74, 82, "PERSON"], [199, 208, "PERSON"], [215, 218, "TIME"]]}],
["What do you got on Korda?", {"entities": [[19, 24, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jesus, that Lynette! I rode her hard and put her up wet.", {"entities": [[12, 19, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Yes, we're in New York now. But where are you planning to stay in New York?", {"entities": [[14, 22, "GPE"], [23, 26, "TIME"]]}],
["Talk to you tomorrow.", {"entities": [[12, 20, "DATE"]]}],
["How's the store?", {"entities": [[10, 15, "LOC"]]}],
["Fuck off, Barry.", {"entities": [[10, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Is that all you guys can think about? Amy never came back last night. Maybe she's in trouble.", {"entities": [[38, 41, "PERSON"], [58, 68, "TIME"]]}],
["But...has anyone seen him in London?", {"entities": [[29, 35, "GPE"]]}],
["My name is Barry Egan and I spoke to you....you called me, you remember?", {"entities": [[11, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["Just do it, Amy, please, go.", {"entities": [[12, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Bully? Are we talking about Gary Boyd? Or your dad.", {"entities": [[28, 37, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now, Amos, now-- What?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"], [5, 9, "PERSON"], [11, 14, "TIME"]]}],
["Rome is going to pay tribute -- like a defeated nation begging for mercy? Have you told your troops that?", {"entities": [[0, 4, "GPE"]]}],
["Oh, Roy, it was great! We were rolling in dough, lived wherever we wanted, only pulled two or three scams a year.", {"entities": [[106, 112, "TIME"], [4, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["Anyway, now we can start looking for the apartment... Do you remember when we first came up with that whole idea of renting our own apartment?", {"entities": [[41, 50, "LOC"], [8, 11, "TIME"]]}],
["Fifty minutes.", {"entities": [[0, 13, "TIME"]]}],
["Come on, Junior, it's a school night.", {"entities": [[31, 36, "TIME"]]}],
["I have to go now.", {"entities": [[13, 16, "TIME"]]}],
["Now, my dear boy. You shouldn't ", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["*No*! I don't want to know him! He's doing *missionary* work--in *India*! I wrote him *weeks* ago, but he's either too holy or too busy to answer. Maybe he got killed in the war!", {"entities": [[66, 71, "GPE"]]}],
["Traitor! Benedict Arnold! Remember Nathan Hale, right, sir?", {"entities": [[35, 46, "PERSON"], [9, 24, "PERSON"]]}],
["Wilbur, the adopting couple is waiting in your office.", {"entities": [[0, 6, "GPE"]]}],
["You're smart, Lilly, and you're good-looking. You won't have any trouble finding a job.", {"entities": [[14, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["You said it like it was a big joke, Bob. Like he's wild.", {"entities": [[36, 39, "PERSON"]]}],
["Bitchin' good cake.", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mr. Smith has been waiting for you and Mrs. Trueworthy. Can you take care of Mr. Smith now?", {"entities": [[44, 54, "PERSON"], [4, 9, "PERSON"], [87, 90, "TIME"]]}],
["Why don't you come home with me? I mean nobody's home at my house--and I'm not tired, are you? I don't have many--people I can talk to.", {"entities": [[60, 65, "LOC"]]}],
["A yert. Ruth is a living legend, Rex. At a time when most women are in Boca, having early bird specials -- she's working so her husband can be in Montana. In a yert.", {"entities": [[8, 12, "PERSON"], [71, 75, "GPE"], [146, 153, "GPE"]]}],
["Poached <u>and</u> over, Captain Oveur? Over.", {"entities": [[33, 38, "PERSON"]]}],
["She's sore hurt, Jack, tis true, but not dead yet.", {"entities": [[17, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, the man of the hour that we all would like to talk to about now has apparently skipped town. And all of a sudden the Smithsonian's ambulence chaser is an expert on missing persons.", {"entities": [[66, 69, "TIME"], [17, 25, "TIME"], [123, 134, "ORG"]]}],
["Well, it's not really mine. I dug it up in front of the courthouse. We're transplanting it. Letting it breathe, you know. But, of course, we would like to get it into soil, as soon as possible.", {"entities": [[173, 192, "TIME"], [56, 66, "LOC"]]}],
["Christ, George, Joseph Reed's been writing letters back to Congress attacking you. Your own aide!", {"entities": [[16, 27, "PERSON"], [8, 14, "PERSON"], [59, 67, "ORG"]]}],
["Doolittle...", {"entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["I didn't ask for any help. Did you, Linda?", {"entities": [[36, 41, "PERSON"]]}],
["Bon soir, mademoiselle!", {"entities": [[0, 8, "ORG"]]}],
["I got caught in the storm. You were gone all night too.", {"entities": [[45, 50, "TIME"]]}],
["Chicago, the passengers are beginning to panic. When do we start down?", {"entities": [[0, 7, "GPE"]]}],
["If you tell him, you'll probably make summer associate. Who cares about Brooke? Think about yourself.", {"entities": [[72, 78, "PERSON"], [38, 44, "TIME"]]}],
["Julia's my second wife.", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["I looked for you in my closet tonight. It's crazy, I don't know where you came from, but I like you.", {"entities": [[30, 37, "TIME"]]}],
["Busy night for a Tuesday. We had a busload of retired folks in on a wine tour. Usually they're not too rowdy, but tonight there was something going on. Full moon or something. What can I get you?", {"entities": [[5, 10, "TIME"], [17, 24, "DATE"], [114, 121, "TIME"]]}],
["What the devil do you want? Listen, Bruce, you can't come in here now! We're busy! Where you been, Duffy? Stick around! What? What Chinese earthquake? The deuce with it... what's that?", {"entities": [[66, 69, "TIME"], [36, 41, "PERSON"], [99, 104, "PERSON"]]}],
["Yes, I speak. And read. And think... and know the ways of Man. I've been waiting for you. Two months now.", {"entities": [[90, 100, "TIME"], [42, 45, "TIME"]]}],
["Okay, listen up. As you all know by now, we have an addition to our crew. Dr. Weir, this is: Starck, navigation; Smith, pilot, Justin, ship's engineer --", {"entities": [[93, 99, "GPE"], [33, 39, "TIME"], [113, 118, "PERSON"], [127, 133, "PERSON"]]}],
["[I see him sometimes at the handball court in Chapultepec on a Saturday afternoon.]", {"entities": [[46, 57, "GPE"], [28, 42, "LOC"], [63, 81, "TIME"]]}],
["I'm not too short to be Cagney.", {"entities": [[24, 30, "PERSON"]]}],
["I'm still trying to ditch this Texas Smokey. I don't know what the sucker wants.", {"entities": [[31, 43, "ORG"]]}],
["Hello -- hello! Is this the Lying -- In Hospital? Did you have an auto accident in the last --", {"entities": [[40, 48, "LOC"]]}],
["She starts givin' me some bullshit about it ain't there. It's somewhere else and we can go get it. I'm shootin' you in the head right then and there. Then I'm gonna shoot her in the kneecap, find out where my godamn money is. I go walkin' in there and that nigga Winston or anybody else is in there, you're the first man shot, understand what I'm sayin'?", {"entities": [[263, 270, "GPE"]]}],
["The Bismark in Chicago. You familiar?", {"entities": [[15, 22, "GPE"], [4, 11, "GPE"]]}],
["A gay lot - Redi, for instance. I don't know what her sorrow is, but her life's an empty one. She's had to have this to cling to. Frances Fallon, with her worship of Jacqueline, has had to follow like a sheep. And Bruns, the fanatic. And you...", {"entities": [[130, 144, "PERSON"], [166, 176, "PERSON"], [214, 219, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now you're talking, Babe. I'll keep the whole front page open. What are you going to do?", {"entities": [[20, 24, "PERSON"], [0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Get away, Snorri.", {"entities": [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now, when did you adopt me?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Well, Austin, you've stopped Dr. Evil from destroying the world with his subterranean nuclear probe, and somehow you and Agent Kensington managed to escape unscathed from his evil lair.", {"entities": [[33, 37, "PERSON"], [6, 12, "PERSON"], [127, 137, "GPE"]]}],
["And Mr. Hearst has authorized me to tell you that you're looking at the most beautiful lawsuit in history if you release this picture. He'll bleed your little studio dry and you can all go on back to New York and do Shakespeare with the Boy Wonder.", {"entities": [[8, 14, "PERSON"], [200, 208, "GPE"], [216, 227, "PERSON"]]}],
["Did you find your Franklin Mint egg, Rosemary darling?", {"entities": [[18, 31, "ORG"]]}],
["Dieter's gone to shoot a still job. Hong Kong.", {"entities": [[36, 45, "GPE"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]}],
["Should I wait up? We've got to get up early for the beach tomorrow.", {"entities": [[52, 57, "LOC"], [58, 66, "DATE"]]}],
["Tell me, Doolittle, how are the Dodgers doing?", {"entities": [[9, 18, "PERSON"], [32, 39, "ORG"]]}],
["David, stop stressing, you can like-- turn it on normally ...", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["But we do know that the people of that region of Asia Minor, from the Tigris-Euphrates valley to the Mediterranean, are dark-skinned people. I've studied drawings and photographs and seen newsreels. I have never seen a native of that area who was not black.", {"entities": [[101, 114, "GPE"], [49, 59, "GPE"]]}],
["No, we don't! You're full of shit! You say you want to end the war, so why don't you? My brother died over there last November. Why? What good was his death?", {"entities": [[113, 126, "TIME"]]}],
["What can I say? It's jail. You don't sleep when you want to. You don't eat when you want to.", {"entities": [[21, 25, "LOC"]]}],
["Six months, maybe five, five or six months...do you wanna check that?", {"entities": [[32, 42, "TIME"], [0, 10, "TIME"]]}],
["Our guest tonight is the extraordinary, talented performer, Mantan. Thanks for coming in.", {"entities": [[10, 17, "TIME"], [60, 66, "PERSON"]]}],
["She grabbed herself a perfect running mate. King Westley! The pill of the century! What she needs is a guy that'd take a sock at her every day whether it's coming to her or not.", {"entities": [[133, 142, "TIME"], [49, 56, "PERSON"]]}],
["A locker at the airport? Jesus Christ, Harry. Tell me you're not really that stupid.", {"entities": [[39, 44, "PERSON"], [16, 23, "LOC"], [25, 37, "PERSON"]]}],
["Uhura is busy. I am monitoring.", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Young man, I am no stranger to theatres. I'm no stranger to insolence!", {"entities": [[31, 39, "LOC"]]}],
["Ignorance! I believe the Indies are no more than 750 leagues west of the Canary Islands.", {"entities": [[73, 87, "GPE"]]}],
["Anthony, we're on the run. This is an emergency. It's only fair that...", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jeez, Mrs. Raymond, that was eleven years ago.", {"entities": [[11, 18, "PERSON"], [29, 45, "DATE"]]}],
["Beaumont worked for you.", {"entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ever since you've looked after Steve you've had the dream -- a ranch on the river -- good grass, good water, barn corral and house --- that part you've shared with Steve. The girl in gingham you plan sneakin' in when he isn't looking. ", {"entities": [[63, 68, "LOC"], [31, 36, "PERSON"], [76, 81, "LOC"], [125, 130, "LOC"]]}],
["Come on, come on. What are you trying to do, kid? Keel over? You haven't been out of this house in two weeks.", {"entities": [[90, 95, "LOC"], [96, 108, "DATE"]]}],
["Now listen to me, Pearl. You and me is runnin' off tonight.", {"entities": [[51, 58, "TIME"], [0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Goddamn Venza assaulted a taxi driver in the Bronx, thirteen months ago. It's coming to court and the judge let him walk because of the pending case law.", {"entities": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [45, 50, "GPE"], [52, 71, "DATE"]]}],
["I need your help, Joyce.", {"entities": [[18, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
["Two minutes, ten seconds.", {"entities": [[0, 24, "TIME"]]}],
["Sounds like a two weeks' notice to me.", {"entities": [[14, 23, "TIME"]]}],
["Yeah. Like I said, I don't want to take sides. And I like Laura with you. She's more fun, more open. You guys are good together. I just wish you two could, I don't know. I don't think much of this Ian guy --", {"entities": [[58, 63, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mrs. Wheeler is dead.", {"entities": [[5, 12, "PERSON"]]}],
["It's an animal urge, Puff. It's nothing to be ashamed of.", {"entities": [[21, 25, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, at the expense of some of the furniture, Susan--you've made another conquest.", {"entities": [[47, 52, "PERSON"]]}],
["The Countess has come to our aid. The Rubber Rose Ranch is officially deeded to all the cowgirls. And I have been asked to oversee the ranch. For $300 a week. And as it turns out, the Countess is not going to be the vegetable the doctors thought he was... here's a picture!", {"entities": [[135, 140, "LOC"], [50, 55, "LOC"], [151, 157, "TIME"]]}],
["She was in a great fortress, first in the mountains, then in the jungle. How is that possible?", {"entities": [[65, 71, "LOC"], [19, 27, "LOC"], [42, 51, "LOC"]]}],
["Frank doesn't take to most people. Do you speak German?", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mrs. Peel ... Come quickly. Brolly's been betrayed! I'll tell you everything ... The weather's getting worse and worse ... they're after me ... coming for me ... come quickly!", {"entities": [[5, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["We saw it in the office. It went from this big... to big... in a day.", {"entities": [[60, 68, "DATE"], [17, 23, "LOC"]]}],
["He took his stuff. He's gone. I should of seen this. I should of expected it. Bob doesn't have any character.", {"entities": [[78, 81, "PERSON"]]}],
["Todd? Todd doesn't know either.", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["No. I told you. I don't want to hurt you. I want to help you. I think I know some of what is happening to you. Dorothy? Frank has your husband and son. Dorothy? Doesn't he? You have to do something Dorothy. Go to the police.", {"entities": [[120, 125, "PERSON"], [111, 118, "PERSON"]]}],
["Twenty-five more'n I got.", {"entities": [[0, 11, "TIME"]]}],
["[You are Jorge Ramirez.]", {"entities": [[9, 22, "PERSON"]]}],
["I wish you everything I couldn't give you, Hildy.", {"entities": [[43, 48, "PERSON"]]}],
["This is the most amusing thing I have ever heard and with a bit of gossip to season it your failure with Jacqueline. Has she returned to her husband?", {"entities": [[105, 115, "PERSON"]]}],
["In the house?", {"entities": [[7, 12, "LOC"]]}],
["I had love in my heart. And I gave it to one woman. And she gone now. Where am I gonna put all this love?", {"entities": [[65, 68, "TIME"]]}],
["You're new to Charenton, yes? Perhaps you're not yet familiar with my husband, and his unusual case.", {"entities": [[14, 23, "GPE"]]}],
["The guy's setting you up. You pulled out of their Freaks deal so he's paying you back.", {"entities": [[50, 56, "ORG"]]}],
["Because I'm really trying, you know. Rosie says maybe only another two years of the elctrolysis.", {"entities": [[67, 76, "TIME"], [37, 42, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mike. I want you to know that I'm pregnant.", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Letterman show, NBC. We'll talk then. Bye.", {"entities": [[16, 19, "ORG"], [0, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["In the middle of the night -- those flowers make me think of a funeral. Laurels and tube-roses. Oh, think, Suzette -- the Villa and the sun at Tremezzo -- quiet -- simple -- happy -- we'll have a guest, Suzette.", {"entities": [[122, 127, "LOC"], [21, 26, "TIME"], [107, 114, "PERSON"], [143, 151, "ORG"]]}],
["Some Indian tracker you turned out to be, Tom.", {"entities": [[42, 45, "PERSON"]]}],
["Tomorrow I'll talk to your probation officer. Karen's a good kid, but she's mad at you, because you lied to her. This business about your grandmother's funeral", {"entities": [[46, 51, "PERSON"], [0, 8, "DATE"]]}],
["Now, Carnes, listen to me. Listen very, very carefully. I killed Paul Owen and I liked it. I can't make myself any clearer", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"], [5, 11, "PERSON"], [65, 74, "PERSON"]]}],
["So -- are you making any New Year's resolutions?", {"entities": [[25, 35, "DATE"]]}],
["You...you shouldn't have come. I don't have time now.", {"entities": [[49, 52, "TIME"]]}],
["Just, I mean, well, you're here every single day.", {"entities": [[38, 48, "DATE"]]}],
["You're gonna hit some heavy precipitation in about six minutes. Better let your flaps down, these roads are killers when they're damp.", {"entities": [[51, 62, "TIME"]]}],
["What was the cover on the one that got Holden?", {"entities": [[39, 45, "PERSON"]]}],
["What did you do to him? He's been like this all night!", {"entities": [[48, 53, "TIME"]]}],
["Come on, John. What happened?", {"entities": [[9, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't know... about half an hour.", {"entities": [[22, 34, "TIME"]]}],
["Not at all. That's Alexander Hamilton's idea[5] - the finest banking mind this country has ever known. Those are his exact words, gentlemen. Character! It's the only thing you can bank on, and it's the only thing that will pull this country out of the doldrums.", {"entities": [[19, 37, "PERSON"]]}],
["I'm still can't believe you didn't tell Donovan the alibi.", {"entities": [[40, 47, "PERSON"]]}],
["There's one more thing, Austin.", {"entities": [[24, 30, "GPE"]]}],
["Sure. Bettina Peterson. Marfa, Texas. Let's run a current check.", {"entities": [[24, 29, "GPE"], [6, 22, "PERSON"], [31, 36, "GPE"]]}],
["Maybe there's more to this, Susie. The CIA's keeping something from our enemies.", {"entities": [[39, 42, "ORG"], [28, 33, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now, don't tell me you fell in love with a bus driver!", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Games? Look at me closely, Patterson: I am a monster. My only pleasure is tormenting people who work for me, such as yourself. One mistake and I promise you this: I'll make you hate me.", {"entities": [[27, 36, "PERSON"]]}],
["What is ridiculous? Wolfi has many admirers in Vienna. They love him here. People send us gifts all the time.", {"entities": [[47, 53, "GPE"], [20, 25, "PERSON"]]}],
["Our families, Fred. I've always looked on Bessie as my own sister.", {"entities": [[14, 18, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"]]}],
["Theo, did you see the animal?", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Helen, tell Matt I want to see him.", {"entities": [[12, 18, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ah, I see...Yes. Paul's disappearance...Yes.", {"entities": [[17, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["I think Clinton is a breakthrough. Shaw denies he knows Ferrie or Oswald. Is that right? It proves he's a liar. Keep on it, Bill. ", {"entities": [[8, 15, "PERSON"], [35, 39, "PERSON"]]}],
["We saved him! Saved him before the creature could finish his work. Now leave, all of you, quickly, before he finishes you all.", {"entities": [[67, 70, "TIME"]]}],
["This afternoon before I came here. He was with Ordell at an apartment in Hermosa Beach. I don't know if he lives there, but I can find out.", {"entities": [[47, 53, "PERSON"], [0, 14, "TIME"], [60, 69, "LOC"], [73, 86, "GPE"]]}],
["Honey, can we talk tonight? You know, about stuff? Things have been so strained for the past three weeks, since you know, and I just want to talk.", {"entities": [[88, 104, "TIME"], [19, 26, "TIME"]]}],
["Very amateurish, Peter. I'm surprised you would use such an obvious tactic. I'm not an idiot! Don't treat me as one! I'll call you everyday... You get one minute, whether you put me on hold or talk is up to you! Are you ready to play?", {"entities": [[151, 161, "TIME"], [17, 22, "PERSON"], [131, 139, "TIME"]]}],
["Yeah. Keep a closer eye on her -- And him. Shootin' going on, we'll never find Lednov.", {"entities": [[43, 50, "PERSON"], [79, 85, "PERSON"]]}],
["For five years I paid for your stupidness - you'll carry my bag for the rest of my life if I say so. Unless you refuse, Oleg.", {"entities": [[4, 14, "TIME"], [120, 124, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jesus Christ on the cross... Someone make sense.", {"entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"]]}],
["No man No!! Tyrone listen... we got to move man, they got a warehouse...", {"entities": [[12, 18, "GPE"]]}],
["If we don't strike soon, there may not be much of an America left to defend.", {"entities": [[53, 60, "GPE"]]}],
["It's Spanish. It means... 'I don't want to die.' Not all the ghosts are scary, are they? Like Mrs. Marschal?", {"entities": [[99, 107, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ooh! A kind of recent record! Rob's sly declaration of new classic-status slipped into a list of old classics! Nice! ", {"entities": [[30, 33, "PERSON"]]}],
["I am ashamed to put the picture of Lenin in a room like this. Comrades, your telegram was received with great disfavor in Moscow.", {"entities": [[35, 40, "PERSON"], [46, 50, "LOC"], [122, 128, "GPE"]]}],
["That's why you never liked me. I'm different from you. Well, everything's different now, so it doesn't matter. So there.", {"entities": [[84, 87, "TIME"]]}],
["They burn many villages. Even walled cities fall to them.", {"entities": [[15, 23, "LOC"], [44, 48, "TIME"]]}],
["Ma'am, Ray Dunbar's black.", {"entities": [[7, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["...that was Vicki, her best friend. Dat dress will cast ya round...", {"entities": [[12, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["Okay, yeah. I did something naughty... There's this amazing Comix store in Seattle. To tell you the truth, I did it once or twice at Stanford. 'Guess I can't keep anything from you...", {"entities": [[60, 71, "LOC"], [75, 82, "GPE"], [133, 141, "ORG"]]}],
["June twenty-third, '72, sir. The part that's underlined. Your instructions to Haldeman regarding the CIA and the FBI.", {"entities": [[78, 86, "PERSON"], [0, 17, "DATE"], [101, 104, "ORG"], [113, 116, "ORG"]]}],
["Where you goin' tonight?", {"entities": [[16, 23, "TIME"]]}],
["Not really. They just said it might be because we trained at Houston and they trained in Marshall, and that we're being charged against differ- ent accounting offices.", {"entities": [[61, 68, "GPE"], [89, 97, "GPE"]]}],
["But I'll tell you something, what I said in their, still goes. You and your family have been through a lot in the last two days... Not to mention what happened to you all seven months ago.", {"entities": [[114, 127, "TIME"], [171, 187, "DATE"]]}],
["What is it, now? Tell me...", {"entities": [[12, 15, "TIME"]]}],
["Your son-in-law dealt with the dry cleaning franchise during the day, saw that woman every night. The specifics are in the report, and information about the woman. It's unpleasant, I know. I apologize...", {"entities": [[85, 96, "TIME"], [61, 68, "DATE"]]}],
["And this?! Good Lord, have you lost your mind? Nixon can't say this. ", {"entities": [[47, 52, "PERSON"]]}],
["Dr. Jones -- I want Nurhachi.", {"entities": [[20, 28, "PERSON"], [4, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["Christian Reformed. It's a Dutch Calvinist denomination.", {"entities": [[0, 18, "ORG"]]}],
["I promised Iran to Townsend.", {"entities": [[11, 15, "GPE"], [19, 27, "GPE"]]}],
["I'm going to play poker until three a.m. or until the patient is ready for surgery. However, if you'd like to operate on him yourself right now, be my guest. I get the same dough whether I work or not.", {"entities": [[134, 143, "TIME"], [24, 40, "TIME"]]}],
["That, my dear Conway, is the story of a remarkable man.", {"entities": [[14, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["George, remember that night when we were drinking with Arnold?", {"entities": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [22, 27, "TIME"], [55, 61, "PERSON"]]}],
["I got a bad feelin', Llewelyn.", {"entities": [[21, 29, "PERSON"]]}],
["You thought about it too. You've been suspicious for a while. But it's not happening in there. It's happening in the Day Care.", {"entities": [[113, 120, "DATE"]]}],
["Yeah! He'd kill for you Dave. He likes you. Your mind.", {"entities": [[24, 28, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now, you said the gravitational forces in this sector have been altered, could that also affect the course of the ribbon?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["It's not the English way, for ladies to have two lovers, and, so, Mr. Dugan, I'll thank you to pay me the sum you owe me, and I resign all claims to this young lady. If she has a fancy for school-boys, let her take 'em, sir.", {"entities": [[70, 75, "PERSON"]]}],
["There are more this year than last.", {"entities": [[15, 24, "TIME"]]}],
["I'm not talking celebrity, vanity, CBS. I'm talking about when you're nearer the end of your life than the beginning. Now, what do you think you think about then? The future? ", {"entities": [[35, 38, "ORG"]]}],
["We always knew you'd come to us, Louis.", {"entities": [[33, 38, "PERSON"]]}],
["You said he had two days' start. That he would blend in. Disappear!", {"entities": [[16, 24, "TIME"]]}],
["We are trying to stand out. Right near his address. Easier to get them to come to us, than to try and find them. ..now keep your eyes open, something might present itself.", {"entities": [[115, 118, "TIME"]]}],
["What are you doing? Get Connell at the Bulletin ! Why, he's liable to go right past my window, What was that?!", {"entities": [[24, 31, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, what I wanna do is go back to work. But I got this Scagnetti prick deep up my ass. He won't let me leave the halfway house till I get some piece of shit job. My plans have always been to be part of the team again.", {"entities": [[123, 128, "LOC"], [57, 66, "PERSON"]]}],
["That's it. You're that policeman with friends in low places. Tell me, how's Guissepe Torres doing these days? Those racketeering indictments must have really been a downer --", {"entities": [[76, 91, "PERSON"]]}],
["Have I trespassed on a male prerogative? We're being followed. I saw him at Trubshaw's ...", {"entities": [[76, 84, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mine's Edward. And truthfully, I do want you to leave, Karl. But I want to leave with you. You think this town is too small for you, well, it's too small for a man of my ambition. I can't see staying here a day longer.", {"entities": [[7, 13, "PERSON"], [55, 59, "PERSON"], [205, 210, "TIME"]]}],
["Oh NY god... oh my god... oh my god...", {"entities": [[3, 5, "GPE"]]}],
["Shush, Adele.", {"entities": [[7, 12, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "GPE"]]}],
["Then you don't see him for a few days?", {"entities": [[27, 37, "TIME"]]}],
["Pinot noir? Not again! You know, not all Pinots are noir.", {"entities": [[41, 47, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, bomb, we have about sixty seconds to drop. Just wondering if everything is all right. Have you checked your platinum euridium energy shielding?", {"entities": [[26, 39, "TIME"]]}],
["He's gay -- he isn't Brooke's lover! He's making it up. Whoever killed Heyworth is paying him off.", {"entities": [[21, 27, "PERSON"], [71, 79, "GPE"]]}],
["Now Tom, you simply cannot go to Philadelphia tonight. That's all there is to it.", {"entities": [[4, 7, "PERSON"], [0, 3, "TIME"], [33, 45, "GPE"], [46, 53, "TIME"]]}],
["We've never had a fight. Not a real one. But we're going to have one right now if you don't talk about it.", {"entities": [[69, 78, "TIME"]]}],
["Mine's Eleanor. Eleanor Schiff.", {"entities": [[16, 30, "PERSON"], [7, 14, "PERSON"]]}],
["We'd better get back now.", {"entities": [[21, 24, "TIME"]]}],
["You know, this is kind of embarrassing, but my wallet was stolen yesterday and I'm afraid the ticket was in it. But the name's Pearson.", {"entities": [[65, 74, "DATE"], [127, 134, "PERSON"]]}],
["S'alright. I'm sorry too. Shit, I gotta take a leak... Pull over at that gas station.", {"entities": [[73, 84, "LOC"]]}],
["Fine. I thought you were leaving today.", {"entities": [[33, 38, "DATE"]]}],
["Josephine dead -- how unbelievable! How impossible it is to believe it. She was always physically so strong -- she was never ill a day in her life.", {"entities": [[129, 134, "TIME"], [0, 9, "GPE"]]}],
["Every week we follow the trials and tribulations of two real coons - Mantan and Sleep 'n Eat. The Dusky Duo.", {"entities": [[0, 10, "TIME"]]}],
["See -- she's just having some water. Now there's no need for the cops or anything.", {"entities": [[37, 40, "TIME"]]}],
["Don't do this to me now, Joel. Really.", {"entities": [[25, 29, "PERSON"], [20, 23, "TIME"]]}],
["You tell lies, Dad. You tell amusing lies. Stories are what you tell a five-year old at bedtime. They're not elaborate mythologies you maintain when your son is ten and fifteen and twenty and thirty. And the thing is, I believed you. I believed your stories so much longer than I should have. And then when I realized that everything you said was impossible -- everything! -- I felt like such a fool to have trusted you. You were like Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny combined. Just as charming and just as fake.", {"entities": [[71, 80, "TIME"], [455, 461, "DATE"]]}],
["And making you feel bad at the same time, huh? But that's the way I am, you know, the way I've always been. Always picking on poor little Roy.", {"entities": [[138, 141, "PERSON"]]}],
["I went with Sandy and Vera. Salvy was there. Stop it. I just had a drink, that's all. I didn't do anything wrong. ", {"entities": [[28, 33, "PERSON"]]}],
["Chief, here's a little secret. Drink heavily, your feet will know what to do. Now shit or get off the pot. Do you wanna dance or do you wanna see KISS only on their album covers?", {"entities": [[78, 81, "TIME"]]}],
["Really? I'm the only person I know that likes Danny Ainge, outside of Celtic fans. Maybe Phoenix.", {"entities": [[89, 96, "GPE"], [46, 57, "PERSON"]]}],
["Fuck you, Roy Ostrey!", {"entities": [[10, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["Knock it off. Now.", {"entities": [[14, 17, "TIME"]]}],
["Something's been going on here in Europe. And it's still going on. Post Conklin. Who's been in Berlin?", {"entities": [[67, 79, "ORG"], [34, 40, "GPE"], [95, 101, "GPE"]]}],
["There are no answers. There's either Jason Bourne alive or Jason Bourne dead. And I for one would prefer the latter. And what about her? You just send her out to this lunatic with no protection?", {"entities": [[37, 49, "PERSON"]]}],
["Was. You ain't afraid of ghosts, now are you?", {"entities": [[33, 36, "TIME"]]}],
["I was just wondering if you thought there'd by any other gorgeous women at Camp Crystal Lake. Besides yourself.", {"entities": [[75, 92, "GPE"]]}],
["How are you, Benjamin?", {"entities": [[13, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't know... I'm sorry, but Dana's a very jealous person. I just don't want to screw that up right now... I'm sure she'll dump me soon and we can go back to being friends...", {"entities": [[31, 35, "PERSON"], [96, 105, "TIME"]]}],
["Lemme call him now. Make sure he's not already busy tomorrow night.", {"entities": [[52, 66, "TIME"], [15, 18, "TIME"]]}],
["Now, now, darlin'... Jack just needs to know what business he's in.", {"entities": [[21, 25, "PERSON"], [0, 3, "TIME"], [5, 8, "TIME"]]}],
["They don't see sin in their nakedness. They live according to nature, in a never ending summer. The islands are covered with trees, filled with blossoms and fruits. And...", {"entities": [[88, 94, "TIME"], [100, 107, "LOC"]]}],
["Yeah? Well, she called Sue Ann yesterday from Arizona.", {"entities": [[31, 40, "DATE"], [27, 30, "PERSON"], [46, 53, "GPE"]]}],
["Hello, Natalie. Mr. Stewart Smith . . . Miss Montgomery, Mrs. Eames, Mrs. Radcliff, Mr. Radcliff ", {"entities": [[45, 55, "PERSON"], [20, 33, "PERSON"], [62, 67, "PERSON"], [74, 82, "PERSON"]]}],
["But, my dear Duroc, how can I act without guidance from Vienna? I haven't the slightest idea of how the Emperor Francis might feel about this.", {"entities": [[112, 119, "PERSON"], [56, 62, "GPE"]]}],
["Elaine! Call Chub Meritt and have him pick up Wade's car, fix the clutch.", {"entities": [[13, 24, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [46, 50, "PERSON"]]}],
["Halfdan wanted to stop you waking the Gods... so... I disguised myself to sabotage their plans.", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["To Earth. To offer testimony.", {"entities": [[3, 8, "GPE"]]}],
["We'd like to ask you about a business associate of your, Warren Hubley.", {"entities": [[57, 70, "PERSON"]]}],
["Excellent! Stephen is my name. I'm the most wanted man on the Emerald Isle. Except I'm not on the Emerald Isle of course, more's the pity.", {"entities": [[62, 74, "GPE"], [11, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["Yeah, but if I told her about the other stuff about Frank...", {"entities": [[52, 57, "PERSON"]]}],
["There's a startling question, coming from you. I'm captain of this ship. We sailed from Archangel a month ago, seeking a passage to the North Pole.", {"entities": [[98, 109, "DATE"], [88, 97, "GPE"], [136, 146, "GPE"]]}],
["You're here. Home. The doctor said you're lucky your brains didn't boil. What a night, Jake. It was crazy. You kept sayin' ", {"entities": [[80, 85, "TIME"], [87, 91, "PERSON"], [124, 129, "PERSON"], [255, 265, "TIME"]]}],
["Harry, Harry, Harry...", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Harry? Oh Harry, I knew you'd come. I love you, Harry. I love... Take me home, Harry.", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Take these round now, will you please? The American boy in twenty-one is only to have these after he's eaten. Will you be sure of that?", {"entities": [[17, 20, "TIME"]]}],
["No, Monsieur Varlac, my warrant is only for you. Now, will you please come down at once. You will be taken back to Chalon for trial.", {"entities": [[4, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jim, before this Kennedy thing, nothing mattered to you in this life more than your children. The other night Jasper tried to show you a drawing. You didn't even notice he was there. He came to me bawling his little eyes out. Jim, he's sensitive - he needs more from you.", {"entities": [[17, 24, "PERSON"], [0, 3, "PERSON"], [104, 109, "TIME"], [110, 116, "PERSON"]]}],
["No! Now get outta my face, kid.", {"entities": [[4, 7, "TIME"]]}],
["Well, at least I'm glad to see you have a sense of humor. That's the first smile I've seen on that gloomy face of your's ... ... isn't it? It isn't. Oh no. Oh dear. Oh now I've gone and done it.", {"entities": [[168, 171, "TIME"]]}],
["Hiya Jake. That was some dance.", {"entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["You heard that, Sefton?", {"entities": [[16, 22, "GPE"]]}],
["Saw what, Mr. Cooper? What did you really see, because what you're describing is not physically possible...", {"entities": [[14, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["How you, Walt? We was just fixing to have a nightcap.", {"entities": [[9, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["It's not the press that matters. Nixon's wife is proud of him.", {"entities": [[33, 38, "PERSON"]]}],
["David, let me tell you something. These people don't want to be geeks. They want to be ", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Dreamin's all any of you're gonna be doing if we don't get this boat running.", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["Elaine, when are you going to realize Simon Kurtz put me in here to get me out of the way.", {"entities": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [38, 49, "PERSON"]]}],
["-- Forgive me, Mr. Taransky. I'm just trying to understand. All these films, TV appearances, magazine covers, internet interviews, publicity photos, snapshots from her childhood -- all fake. This is fake, this is fake -- fake, fake, fake, all fake.", {"entities": [[19, 27, "PERSON"]]}],
["Olaf Tryggvason used to throw up on every single voyage... the whole time... non-stop... puke... puke... puke.", {"entities": [[0, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["CARL??? Carl did this?!!", {"entities": [[8, 12, "PERSON"]]}],
["Baby, I got to let this old man win. Keep the faith, and tell Billie I'll see her later.", {"entities": [[62, 68, "PERSON"]]}],
["Tomorrow, I see on the TV weather, it's gonna be nice and warm. You won't need the coat.", {"entities": [[0, 8, "DATE"]]}],
["Officers, officers what can I do for you today? I ain't fried up the birds yet... if that's what you're ring a ding dinging about.", {"entities": [[41, 46, "DATE"]]}],
["Oh come on, Rob. What am I, an idiot? I'm more bothered by Dick's thing. How did this happen, Dick? What rational explanation can there possibly be? What's her name?", {"entities": [[12, 15, "PERSON"], [59, 63, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jack, if the rumors hold and Israel is really the great white whale of snitches, then the mob is looking to put all kinds of bullets into his ass and pour some serious psychotics into the mix to do just that. So what real incentive is there to track him on something as small-time as a skip trace, when it's putting you and yours in the path of severe pain and suffering and an almost certain prelude to doom.", {"entities": [[29, 35, "GPE"], [0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Donovan, Royalton and Levinson.", {"entities": [[9, 17, "GPE"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [22, 30, "PERSON"]]}],
["Kurt!", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Five this week; how many the week before?", {"entities": [[5, 14, "TIME"], [25, 33, "TIME"]]}],
["I know you're not calling Jimmy.", {"entities": [[26, 31, "PERSON"]]}],
["I'll try not to hold you back tomorrow.", {"entities": [[30, 38, "DATE"]]}],
["Amy, just listen. Take Cindy and get out of the house. Do it now. Go to a hotel and stay there...", {"entities": [[0, 3, "PERSON"], [48, 53, "LOC"], [61, 64, "TIME"], [74, 79, "LOC"]]}],
["Call me Charlie.", {"entities": [[8, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now don't be absurd, Smith May I come in?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"], [21, 26, "PERSON"]]}],
["Let's go, Jake, wake up!", {"entities": [[10, 14, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ah -- he's learned, then. Plays things more close to the vest. See, Jack was a cartographer, back in Old England. Somehow he came by the money to commission the Pearl. Hired himself a crew, promised each man an equal share. So, they're forty days out, and the First Mate says, everything's an equal share, that should mean the location of the island, too. So Jack gave up the bearings. That night, there was a mutiny.", {"entities": [[68, 72, "PERSON"], [101, 112, "GPE"], [236, 246, "TIME"], [260, 270, "ORG"], [343, 349, "LOC"], [391, 396, "TIME"]]}],
["Did you know that Ted Bundy's first dog, a collie, was named Lassie? Had you heard this?", {"entities": [[18, 27, "PERSON"]]}],
["It's me. It's Jake. Listen... It's happening. Gordo's landing right now. Meet me at the Euclid... For your cut, I mean. It's... I want you to have it.", {"entities": [[46, 51, "PERSON"], [14, 18, "PERSON"], [62, 71, "TIME"], [88, 94, "PERSON"]]}],
["Few months perhaps. I'm gathering the raw materials even now.", {"entities": [[57, 60, "TIME"], [0, 10, "TIME"]]}],
["This one looks like a Steward. They're not warm, but rigor hasn't set in. This didn't happen all that long ago, Jim.", {"entities": [[112, 115, "PERSON"]]}],
["'Praise Jesus?' That's fucking pushing it, Margaret.", {"entities": [[43, 51, "PERSON"], [8, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, okay. But we don't want more than a couple o' hundred people in on this thing. Now the first thing I want is an exact copy of the John Doe letter in your own handwriting.", {"entities": [[136, 144, "PERSON"], [85, 88, "TIME"]]}],
["Trychticholorate. Then Swayzak can announce Seagrave was a murder.", {"entities": [[23, 30, "PERSON"]]}],
["See, I just take your gun to the morgue and fire it into one of their skulls; then I call every newspaper in the country with the story about how Senator Kendall's gay son went nuts on a training mission --", {"entities": [[154, 161, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "LOC"]]}],
["I have to be home in twenty minutes.", {"entities": [[18, 35, "TIME"]]}],
["Don't worry, Eddie. Me and Larry have been friends a long time, he ain't gonna shoot. We like each other too much.", {"entities": [[27, 32, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ben, I don't know if this thing'll change us back or make us worse. I need you to be patient for a little while longe--", {"entities": [[0, 3, "PERSON"]]}],
["Just a minute, General. Listen, don't let them fool you with all their grand la-de-da. They've all made their money from the war -- mostly from crooked war contracts. They say Citizen Barras has put away millions.", {"entities": [[5, 13, "TIME"]]}],
["Now that that's out of the way... You want the woman, here's how it works. You pull fifty large out of your mattress or wherever, and I make a call to bring her in.", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Don't 'easy Ruiz' me. Y'all turned a Easter egg hunt into a butt-fuck-a- thon. Bring me four eggs Benedict and a mimosa. You all want mimosas?", {"entities": [[37, 43, "DATE"], [12, 16, "PERSON"], [98, 106, "PERSON"]]}],
["Really, Frank? When was that?", {"entities": [[8, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now can I tell?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["I do. It's a fuckin Persian Palace.", {"entities": [[20, 34, "LOC"]]}],
["Do you think this was worth waiting all day to see?", {"entities": [[36, 43, "TIME"]]}],
["Who is this? I'm the one telling you the way it is, okay, asshole? That's who I am. Now you want your three hundred grand or don't you?", {"entities": [[84, 87, "TIME"]]}],
["Seventy-two five. Why do you want this barley pop so bad?", {"entities": [[8, 16, "TIME"]]}],
["I missed you to Mr. Parker.", {"entities": [[20, 26, "PERSON"]]}],
["Good morning, Gaston.", {"entities": [[14, 20, "GPE"]]}],
["Yes... That's the first thing Colleen asked too.", {"entities": [[30, 37, "PERSON"]]}],
["Don't try to run, maggot. Chongo's an all-state track star in every event.", {"entities": [[26, 32, "PERSON"]]}],
["No, they sold the house in 1920 to a millionaire, Uriah Bloodworth.", {"entities": [[18, 23, "LOC"], [27, 31, "TIME"], [50, 66, "PERSON"]]}],
["The High Lama? Who pays any attention to him? The porters laugh at the High Lama. All they want to know is how much gold he will give them. Well, I gave them more gold. I've been stealing it for a year. I'd do anything to get out of this place. To get away from that High Lama - the one who calls himself Father Perrault! Why, he's been insane for years!", {"entities": [[195, 201, "TIME"], [4, 13, "ORG"], [312, 320, "PERSON"]]}],
["Nineteen fifty-eight. It's been traveling twenty-two years to get here. And now it's here. And it's either heads or tails, and you have to say. Call it.", {"entities": [[42, 58, "TIME"], [0, 14, "TIME"], [76, 79, "TIME"]]}],
["That there isn't one, as of today. I had my period. I couldn't believe it. He still wanted to marry me.", {"entities": [[28, 33, "DATE"]]}],
["Shit O dear, Julian. Do you mean to tell me you didn't get it on?", {"entities": [[13, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["I believe both of you now. And I think I might know how to make them go away.", {"entities": [[22, 25, "TIME"]]}],
["For the last time, I don't want it cleaned. Now get the hell out of here!", {"entities": [[44, 47, "TIME"]]}],
["Oh that's just BEAUTIFUL! All the scumbags in the quiet city of Boston start dropping dead and you think it's unrelated?! Greenly, the day I want the Boston Police doing my thinking for me, I will have a fucking tag on my toe! Now, get me a squad car and get me over there. I want the crime scene photos and any witness statements. NOW!", {"entities": [[64, 70, "GPE"], [131, 138, "DATE"], [150, 163, "ORG"], [332, 335, "TIME"]]}],
["Now hold on Rodgers...", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"], [12, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["We were close to something with Kendall.", {"entities": [[32, 39, "PERSON"]]}],
["Okey-doke, Indy! Hold onto your potatoes!", {"entities": [[11, 15, "ORG"]]}],
["How do you draw now?", {"entities": [[16, 19, "TIME"]]}],
["Gee whiz, Boss, you know Mr. Norton told me not to leave him, not even for a minute.", {"entities": [[75, 83, "TIME"], [29, 35, "PERSON"]]}],
["Don't you find that restful?... Why didn't you come last night?", {"entities": [[52, 62, "TIME"]]}],
["Thirty seconds? Isn't that cutting it a little too close?", {"entities": [[0, 14, "TIME"]]}],
["Few minutes. Want to catch the news.", {"entities": [[0, 11, "TIME"]]}],
["Ah, my poor Josephine. She was the most alluring, most glamorous creature I have ever known -- a woman in every sense of the word, and she had the kindest heart in the world. She may have been a liar and a spendthrift, but she had something that was irresistible -- she was a women to her very fingertips... How impossible it is to believe that she is dead.", {"entities": [[12, 21, "GPE"]]}],
["You better just kill me Tyrone. And when Huey gets out, when Oakland's just wall to wall junkies, you tell him you blew away the only chance we all got. I'm sure he'll be real happy about that.", {"entities": [[41, 45, "PERSON"], [24, 30, "GPE"], [61, 68, "GPE"]]}],
["Yeah. But I wasn't there for a second.", {"entities": [[29, 37, "TIME"]]}],
["No, it's not. I thought I was done waiting for Reed... We're all in this together now, Ben.", {"entities": [[82, 85, "TIME"], [87, 90, "PERSON"]]}],
["Oh, wait a minute, Miss Packard.", {"entities": [[24, 31, "PERSON"], [9, 17, "TIME"]]}],
["And...and...Henry Chapman's girl, was it Thelma? No, I can see those cornflower eyes...I've lost your name, my sweetness.", {"entities": [[12, 25, "PERSON"]]}],
["I can make no statement about Manchester at this time.", {"entities": [[30, 40, "GPE"]]}],
["But it's my new tape. My Monday morning tape. I made it last night just for today.", {"entities": [[25, 39, "TIME"], [56, 66, "TIME"], [76, 81, "DATE"]]}],
["But you didn't know she was at my place last night when you were. She came there for the letters of transit. Isn't that true, Ilsa?", {"entities": [[40, 50, "TIME"]]}],
["Shoulda learned with Web. Made it look fun, made it look like an adventure. Got Web killed. Now Jim.", {"entities": [[92, 95, "TIME"], [96, 99, "PERSON"]]}],
["You brought the army into Rome.", {"entities": [[26, 30, "GPE"]]}],
["I had to help get rid of the body. You saw it on the subway. And I warn you, Mary -- go back -- you don't know what you're doing, or what dreadful things you might bring about by looking for your sister. You go back to school - - go back and forget Jacqueline.", {"entities": [[77, 81, "PERSON"], [53, 59, "LOC"], [249, 259, "PERSON"]]}],
["Don't worry, Mr. Twombley, I know where those suckers are. Rain or shine, snow or no snow. I know deer. We'll kill us a buck today. Guaranteed. Before ten.", {"entities": [[17, 25, "PERSON"], [125, 130, "DATE"]]}],
["So it is from the finance company. So it's better than no letter at all. So they want the third payment on the Plymouth. So they want the fourth, the fifth, the sixth and the seventh. So they want the Plymouth.", {"entities": [[111, 119, "GPE"]]}],
["It's a big building where the generals meet. But that's not important right now. They've cleared you of any blame for what happened on that raid. Isn't that good news?", {"entities": [[70, 79, "TIME"]]}],
["It's Tatopoulos.", {"entities": [[5, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Harry, I hate being in love. I don't ever want to be in love again. I just hate it!", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Dentonvale...say, that's for... I'm sorry to hear that, Janet. Look I'm going to let you through, but keep it to yourself, otherwise...", {"entities": [[56, 61, "PERSON"], [0, 10, "GPE"]]}],
["Nurse Humphries was checking my prostate this morning. I got an erection.", {"entities": [[0, 15, "ORG"], [41, 53, "TIME"]]}],
["You know my policy. We don't negotiate with terrorists. If we start now, all of America becomes a target.", {"entities": [[80, 87, "GPE"], [5, 8, "TIME"]]}],
["Already had I.Q. test this year -- but I don't think I never had a...", {"entities": [[22, 31, "TIME"], [12, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["They got a lucky break. Yesterday they were just two German clerks. Today they're the 'Honored Dead'.", {"entities": [[68, 73, "DATE"], [24, 33, "DATE"], [87, 99, "ORG"]]}],
["Well, she's back to earth now. They're all pretty huffed up about your leaving. I think you better go back, kid.", {"entities": [[26, 29, "TIME"]]}],
["Try to think of nothing, Dorothy.", {"entities": [[25, 32, "PERSON"]]}],
["However, Senator Smith is still a member of this Body and as such has equal claim on the attention of the Chair--", {"entities": [[17, 22, "PERSON"]]}],
["Who, Benny's little sister?", {"entities": [[5, 10, "PERSON"]]}],
["I've been listening to the transmission. And I think Houston made a mistake in the translation.", {"entities": [[53, 60, "PERSON"]]}],
["Patience, Colonel Arnold. Active personalities terrify these men. But, congratulations on your victory at Ticonderoga...", {"entities": [[18, 24, "GPE"], [106, 117, "GPE"]]}],
["Hold on a second here.", {"entities": [[8, 16, "TIME"]]}],
["-- but the dogs treed him between Huxley and Kafka.", {"entities": [[45, 50, "PERSON"], [34, 40, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, your pupil is married and living in Mannheim, young man.", {"entities": [[42, 50, "GPE"]]}],
["Sorry, Jack.", {"entities": [[7, 11, "PERSON"]]}],
["She musta kept you inna shadows all night.", {"entities": [[36, 41, "TIME"]]}],
["We'll sleep here tonight. You'll come home with me. We'll let the house, and the lands too; plenty of willing neighbors.", {"entities": [[66, 71, "LOC"], [17, 24, "TIME"]]}],
["I'm saying it's not going to happen. Not when the President is set to turn this into a third-rail issue should I choose to ever campaign against him. He will fry me six ways to Sunday for sending daughters and young mothers off to war -- and, quite possibly, for bringing them back in body bags.", {"entities": [[177, 183, "DATE"]]}],
["Roger, Arctic Warrior. I say again, our records indicate the passenger vessel Chimera was lost at sea. Over.", {"entities": [[98, 101, "LOC"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Oh, Kitty, I don't know. This is so last-minute... Eddie is in New York...", {"entities": [[63, 71, "GPE"]]}],
["They come and go as naked as the day God created them...", {"entities": [[29, 36, "DATE"]]}],
["It would seem that Grissom was destroyed by an enemy attack.", {"entities": [[19, 26, "PERSON"]]}],
["Somewhere in this city. Not here, not here. Tell Penelope I loved her--in my clownish way. And Paul. Tell him to be a healer, by all means.", {"entities": [[95, 99, "PERSON"], [49, 59, "PERSON"]]}],
["Forty-seven people drowned last night off the coast of Vancouver after paying smugglers twenty thousand apiece to get into Canada so they could get work in order to eat. Only they got marched overboard at gunpoint instead.", {"entities": [[55, 64, "GPE"], [27, 37, "TIME"], [46, 51, "LOC"], [123, 129, "GPE"]]}],
["Pinkertons. It's the railroad.", {"entities": [[0, 10, "ORG"]]}],
["You know I can't assign you to this. You're much too close to it. You were much too close to Sam. The department will take care of it.", {"entities": [[93, 96, "PERSON"]]}],
["I had news of you in Dublin. Faith, you've begun early, like your father's son, but I think you could not do better than as you have done. But why did you not write home to your poor mother? She has sent half-a-dozen letters to you in Dublin.", {"entities": [[21, 27, "GPE"]]}],
["You son Thomas and Virginia, they come to my house this afternoon...", {"entities": [[8, 14, "PERSON"], [19, 27, "GPE"], [45, 50, "LOC"], [51, 65, "TIME"]]}],
["Some job. Card filing and cabinet dusting. Four years in this dump and I haven't written anything for Wilson that a wounded yak couldn't do.", {"entities": [[43, 53, "TIME"], [102, 108, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jesus, Rachel, what's got into you?", {"entities": [[7, 13, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["No I'm sorry, now I have to get off the phone....", {"entities": [[14, 17, "TIME"]]}],
["What do we do now?", {"entities": [[14, 17, "TIME"]]}],
["Anna Moss. Mossy. The Mossy Thing. The Swamp Thing. Is she all green and furry?", {"entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["-- make the left -- toward the bridge --", {"entities": [[31, 37, "LOC"]]}],
["In that case, maybe Heyworth got fellated by a brunette and Brooke caught him.", {"entities": [[20, 28, "GPE"], [60, 66, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mike, take it easy...", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Saved all our lives, Doc. None of the Liberty boys would have come home if not for Web Mimms, Doc. God's honest truth.", {"entities": [[87, 92, "PERSON"]]}],
["What do you know about the cop? Tazinari. The one who made the ransom drop with Samuel Ramos?", {"entities": [[80, 92, "PERSON"], [32, 40, "GPE"]]}],
["Goddamn! How long have we had this fucking dog?! Two years, he still doesn't come! We need a dog that looks happy when the press is around.", {"entities": [[49, 58, "TIME"]]}],
["Wallace's? For treason there is no trial. Tomorrow he will be charged, then executed.", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [42, 50, "DATE"]]}],
["You wanted to say hello, eh? I can't believe it. When did you fall outa heaven? Anyone ever tell you you're the most beautiful one here, princess of the pool. You got a baby face. Look at mine. Whatcha wanna meet me for?", {"entities": [[153, 157, "LOC"], [62, 66, "TIME"], [188, 192, "LOC"]]}],
["Um, I'm Jerry... that's Bill... Denise and Mary.", {"entities": [[32, 38, "PERSON"], [43, 47, "PERSON"]]}],
["Over to the morgue and up the hill to the cemetery. Never thought I'd admit it, Claude, but you were right.", {"entities": [[12, 18, "LOC"], [42, 50, "LOC"]]}],
["They're the Scoleri Brothers. I tried them for murder. They were electrocuted up at Ossining in '48. Now they want to kill me.", {"entities": [[12, 28, "ORG"], [84, 92, "GPE"], [101, 104, "TIME"]]}],
["... And you always seemed so smart and everything. Like that report you did on ", {"entities": [[84, 93, "LOC"]]}],
["We didn't talk about this. They took the little boy, Cobb.", {"entities": [[53, 57, "GPE"]]}],
["Oh, Mrs. Crawford don't believe in them!", {"entities": [[9, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["You're supposed to be in Vegas. We have a suite at the Flamingo. I was just about to leave for the airport.", {"entities": [[99, 106, "LOC"], [25, 30, "GPE"]]}],
["It means that due to a man made accident the Chernobyl earthworms are now over seventeen percent larger than they were before. Mutated by seventeen percent?", {"entities": [[70, 73, "TIME"]]}],
["Uncle Bobby?", {"entities": [[6, 11, "PERSON"]]}],
["By bouncing ultra-high frequencies off one of the network satellites, I can send a long-range pulsar signal to within TWO FEET of the Rangers coordinates.", {"entities": [[134, 141, "ORG"]]}],
["Ah, Mrs. Pembroke. I spoke to Mr. Schaffer at the Guaranty. He's going to take care of that mortgage for you . . .", {"entities": [[9, 17, "PERSON"], [34, 42, "PERSON"]]}],
["I guess Vernon T. Waldrip is gonna be goin' on relief. Maybe I'll be able to throw a little patronage his way, get the man a job diggin' ditches or rounding up stray dogs.", {"entities": [[8, 25, "PERSON"]]}],
["You know, Monsieur Mercier, this is all non-sense.", {"entities": [[10, 26, "PERSON"]]}],
["Then this shall be our little secret. Remember that I see into thy soul as God sees. Thou may fool the world. Even thy father. But not me, Richard. Never me.", {"entities": [[90, 93, "TIME"], [139, 146, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now, monsieur, you have no right...", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Do you want to come to my apartment or not?", {"entities": [[26, 35, "LOC"]]}],
["You'd have money every year, so you wouldn't have to work. You can stay at Mount Vernon as long as you want...", {"entities": [[17, 27, "TIME"], [75, 87, "GPE"]]}],
["Hey, tabloids paid Ted Bundy - famous serial killer - half a million for his interview. And how much you think Monica got for writing book about the President coming on to her? It pays to be a killer or a whore in this country. Look, you want magazine or not?", {"entities": [[19, 28, "PERSON"], [111, 117, "PERSON"]]}],
["Sarah Lawrence is on the other side of the country.", {"entities": [[0, 14, "PERSON"]]}],
["Be it fit for your wife, Green Jack?", {"entities": [[31, 35, "PERSON"]]}],
["Oh, Rob. What do you want me to say?", {"entities": [[4, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["Message breaking up, Carol. What's wrong? What's wrong?", {"entities": [[21, 26, "PERSON"]]}],
["You wanna know? Turn on the T.V. Watch the fucking news!", {"entities": [[28, 38, "ORG"]]}],
["Mark my words, by the end of this summer you'll be up to your neck in pussy!", {"entities": [[15, 40, "TIME"]]}],
["I don't know. Sometime. Later. Listen, Rob, would you have sex with me?", {"entities": [[39, 42, "PERSON"]]}],
["Make her come out. And when she does, that's when we gotta be careful. She can't get out of this house. She can't even think she can get out of this house. We just keep them here and keep them quiet for forty-five minutes. And I don't want Joe Pesci here standing over them with his fat sweaty finger on the trigger. That's a sure way for us to end up with two dead bodies and little puffs of smoke burning out of our heads up in Greenhaven. So we're gonna seal the place up. They wanna hole up in here? Fine, we'll help 'em. Make it impossible for them to leave. Once they come out of that room.", {"entities": [[97, 102, "LOC"], [203, 221, "TIME"], [240, 249, "PERSON"], [430, 440, "GPE"]]}],
["I've got to stop in there... Mr. Korda, do you know Frank Antonucci?", {"entities": [[33, 38, "PERSON"], [52, 67, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, they needed immediate answers, Frances. It's good manners and good sense. You shouldn't be bothering yourself with these right now.", {"entities": [[127, 136, "TIME"]]}],
["Don't take any guff from these swine. Now we need a sound store with the finest equipment. Nothing dinky. One of those new Belgian Heliowatts with a voice-activated shotgun mike, for picking up conversations in oncoming cars.", {"entities": [[38, 41, "TIME"], [123, 130, "GPE"]]}],
["Mr. Powers, please. I know that you must be a little confused, but we have a very serious situation at hand. I would appreciate it if you'd concentrate on our mission and give your libido a rest.", {"entities": [[4, 10, "PERSON"]]}],
["It's Sanskrit. It tells the story of Sankara climbing Mt. Kalisa where he met the Hindu god Shiva.", {"entities": [[54, 64, "GPE"], [37, 44, "PERSON"]]}],
["That's a 1992 Byron. It's really rare. Don't open it now. I've been saving it!", {"entities": [[14, 19, "PERSON"], [9, 13, "TIME"], [53, 56, "TIME"]]}],
["What can I tell you, Louis? After Nam I didn't want to think anymore. I decided my brain was too small an organ to comprehend this chaos.", {"entities": [[34, 39, "PERSON"], [21, 26, "PERSON"]]}],
["Sure. You shouted at me in the auditorium when I read my essay.", {"entities": [[31, 41, "LOC"]]}],
["It's a place where the dead speak, Missy.", {"entities": [[35, 40, "PERSON"]]}],
["Calm down everybody. We're just here to negotiate General Sarris' surrender.", {"entities": [[58, 64, "PERSON"]]}],
["Uh, Matthew...", {"entities": [[4, 11, "PERSON"]]}],
["We must write to her today, and you can tell her that you are safe and married to ", {"entities": [[21, 26, "DATE"]]}],
["Dr. Sutphin is your wife a big reader?", {"entities": [[4, 11, "PERSON"]]}],
["What's the idea, Anne?", {"entities": [[17, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["We're only on the fucking list for Marie's gig at the Pulaski Pub, that's all! All three of us.", {"entities": [[35, 40, "PERSON"], [54, 65, "LOC"]]}],
["I'm not the only one in there. I got you, Vic, Ben, Johnny, all rattling around in there.", {"entities": [[47, 50, "PERSON"], [52, 58, "PERSON"]]}],
["Pete, the personal rancor reflected in that remark I don't intend to dignify with comment, but I would like to address your general attitude of hopeless negativism. Consider the lilies a the goddamn field, or-hell!- take a look at Delmar here as your paradigm a hope.", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [231, 237, "GPE"]]}],
["Colonel, wait a minute, they may be here now! Say George, get down on that field and guide those planes in when they get here.", {"entities": [[41, 44, "TIME"], [14, 22, "TIME"], [50, 56, "PERSON"]]}],
["Around. Barnett's tough competition.", {"entities": [[8, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["You know! You've got the brain of a pancake! That wasn't just a story you covered -- it was a revolution! Hildy! This is the greatest yarn in journalism since Livingstone discovered Stanley for the New York Herald! ", {"entities": [[106, 111, "PERSON"], [159, 170, "PERSON"], [182, 189, "GPE"], [198, 213, "ORG"]]}],
["Excellency, may I present my niece.", {"entities": [[0, 10, "PERSON"]]}],
["Right - for the first time this year.", {"entities": [[27, 36, "TIME"]]}],
["That's the whole point, Jeffrey. That's the whole point. Anyone's. Everyone's. They are gonna look under every rock, dig up every flaw, every mistake you've ever made. They are going to distort and exaggerate everything you've ever done, man. Don't you understand?", {"entities": [[24, 31, "PERSON"]]}],
["Do what you do to Simone.", {"entities": [[18, 24, "GPE"]]}],
["Dance, Jack! The night's but begun.", {"entities": [[7, 11, "PERSON"], [17, 22, "TIME"]]}],
["ALL I'm saying is dock with Space Lab, couple of hours no more. Let them take a look at our friends.", {"entities": [[39, 54, "TIME"], [28, 37, "LOC"]]}],
["Oh, I'm sorry, Gus! My foot must have slipped.", {"entities": [[15, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["And we're going right to the flea market to get another one! Misty tells me there's a whole booth of Franklin Mint stuff. Dottie, you lock up. I'll take care of poor Rosemary!", {"entities": [[122, 128, "PERSON"], [101, 114, "ORG"]]}],
["An adult bookstore. He was very excited about seeing it. You think home is under a dirty bookstore in the Valley?", {"entities": [[9, 18, "LOC"]]}],
["Marv, let's get Ronnie set up here.", {"entities": [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Boy, the nuts are out tonight. What'd that creep call you - ?", {"entities": [[22, 29, "TIME"]]}],
["I hope you don't mind, Jesse James told me your name.", {"entities": [[23, 34, "PERSON"]]}],
["Did Confucius say that?", {"entities": [[4, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["You went to see Mrs. Redi... She told you something -- what was it?", {"entities": [[21, 25, "PERSON"]]}],
["I'm not pregnant. I got my period this morning. There's no baby, Sid.", {"entities": [[65, 68, "PERSON"], [34, 46, "TIME"]]}],
["I can't work in a vacuum. Why don't you make Hendricks Chief? His family's been here since the Puritans -- half this island are his cousins.", {"entities": [[117, 123, "LOC"], [45, 54, "PERSON"]]}],
["Granger and Pitts are already on it.", {"entities": [[0, 7, "GPE"], [12, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["He's right. Maybe it's time to go to the hang-out route, John. A full and thorough investigation ... We've cooperated with the FBI, we'll cooperate with the Senate. What do we have to hide?", {"entities": [[57, 61, "PERSON"], [127, 130, "ORG"], [157, 163, "ORG"]]}],
["You should have been with us in Nursery, Daniel. I'm positive I recognized him --", {"entities": [[41, 47, "PERSON"]]}],
["Don't beg, Peter. She has to die. I can't win unless she dies.", {"entities": [[11, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["Oh, they're all right, Anne. But I ", {"entities": [[23, 27, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ten grand! I mean, what other poolroom is there in the country where a guy can walk out with ten grand in one night? Jeez, you know, I can remember hustling an old man for a dime a game.", {"entities": [[110, 115, "TIME"]]}],
["Kind of. I mean, John's like this kind of... craftsman. Like he's a carpenter, and he makes really good tables. But that's all he can make, and I don't need anymore tables.", {"entities": [[17, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["About four weeks.", {"entities": [[6, 16, "TIME"]]}],
["I just hope those plates aren't radioactive by tomorrow morning.", {"entities": [[44, 63, "TIME"]]}],
["I'm stayin', Homer.", {"entities": [[13, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["Free to come and go as you please. There's some ", {"entities": [[60, 72, "TIME"]]}],
["Jesus Christ.", {"entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"]]}],
["Three years I've worked for the railroad. Now I don't know why. It seemed a good idea once.", {"entities": [[0, 11, "TIME"], [42, 45, "TIME"]]}],
["Now don't argue, Hildy. How about it, Judge?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"], [17, 22, "PERSON"]]}],
["What have you got for me today? Let me see.", {"entities": [[25, 30, "DATE"]]}],
["It's the maintenance entrance. Runs along the side of the tunnel. When they repaired it last year I worked on a piece about it.", {"entities": [[88, 97, "TIME"], [58, 64, "LOC"]]}],
["Bonanza Jellybean?", {"entities": [[0, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["Yeah 3cpo, I saw STAR WARS, now how about you help me get out of this coffin, Barbie...", {"entities": [[78, 84, "PERSON"], [28, 31, "TIME"]]}],
["May I come in?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Whaddaya got, Nolan?", {"entities": [[14, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["David, before we go in there I want you to know that - no matter what happens to us - it's your fault.", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Were you in the men's room at the Edmonson Drive In Flea Market on Saturday, September 19th?", {"entities": [[67, 91, "DATE"], [22, 26, "LOC"]]}],
["Well, thank you, Mr. Bateman.", {"entities": [[21, 28, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't know, Harry. I... I want so many...", {"entities": [[14, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well gee--how--how've you been, Saunders? I--I haven't seen you in-- . I suppose--now that you're married--", {"entities": [[32, 40, "PERSON"], [82, 85, "TIME"]]}],
["Wilson, do you believe this? Take the damn water.", {"entities": [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]}],
["This is America. There is nothing you can not buy.", {"entities": [[8, 15, "GPE"]]}],
["Linda. That girl looks just like Pat Benatar.", {"entities": [[33, 44, "PERSON"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Ayuh--they get older as you go toward the middle. Pete LaVasseur's dog is buried there... the Stoppard boys' racing pigeon that Missus Cowley's cat got...and I think that's the cat himself right there, although it's been so many years I can't tell for sure. Missy Ellen! Come over here just a minute!", {"entities": [[50, 64, "PERSON"], [94, 102, "PERSON"], [128, 141, "PERSON"], [258, 269, "PERSON"], [291, 299, "TIME"]]}],
["I-it's all right, Mrs. Brewster. It was just a sea-gull. Er. nothing's happened yet! No, I'm watching. Don't worry. Ju-just leave it all to me!", {"entities": [[23, 31, "PERSON"]]}],
["So, the guy goes to Hell and the devil says, ", {"entities": [[112, 119, "DATE"], [20, 24, "GPE"], [129, 134, "TIME"]]}],
["I called Richard Scruggs in Mississippi...", {"entities": [[28, 39, "GPE"], [9, 24, "PERSON"]]}],
["Neither does Henry Blake. But I'll tell you what makes him the best C.O. you've got in any of your hospitals. He leaves all the medical decisions to the men who do the day- to-day work and understand what meatball surgery is.", {"entities": [[164, 171, "DATE"], [13, 24, "PERSON"], [99, 108, "LOC"]]}],
["This is my Uncle Roy, Sebastian.", {"entities": [[22, 31, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["Yes. This is from the twins, Arthur and Dashiel. Agatha's stream was missing. Now this one is from the cyberparlor. Anderton downloaded it directly from Agatha. Watch...", {"entities": [[78, 81, "TIME"], [29, 35, "PERSON"], [49, 55, "PERSON"], [116, 124, "PERSON"]]}],
["Yes it did. Mr. Dunn, can I ask you a personal question?", {"entities": [[16, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["I hear Twombley got shot.", {"entities": [[7, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["One royal pupil and the whole of Vienna will come flocking. We'd be set up for life!", {"entities": [[33, 39, "GPE"]]}],
["C'mon, Rebecca, you wanted it. Now get up there. Ride it side-saddle if you have to -- like a horse. C'mon, now.", {"entities": [[31, 34, "TIME"], [2, 5, "DATE"], [108, 111, "TIME"]]}],
["I expected that two months ago, and they're wasting their time... The bad news is the National Guard has just asked me to resign after 18 years. Well, maybe that's good news - it was never as good as combat, but this is. Bill, any more on Oswald and Shaw?", {"entities": [[129, 143, "TIME"], [16, 30, "DATE"], [86, 100, "ORG"], [250, 254, "PERSON"]]}],
["I've been hired as an independent contractor by the U.S. Resource Center for Missing Persons as part of an internal audit. If you have any time over the next few days, I'd like to make an appointment to ask some questions about the disappearance of your daughter.", {"entities": [[153, 166, "TIME"], [52, 92, "ORG"]]}],
["Norrington, think about it ... the Black Pearl, its captain and crew ... the last pirate threat in the Caribbean. How can you pass that up?", {"entities": [[103, 112, "GPE"], [0, 10, "PERSON"]]}],
["Houdini mice.", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["You're his Lt., Stephen... Are you gonna handle it? Are you Stephen?", {"entities": [[16, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
["Awright. Fire-team A. Gear up. Let's move. Two minutes. Somebody wake up Hicks.", {"entities": [[43, 54, "TIME"], [73, 78, "PERSON"]]}],
["At 7:30 Sunday morning? It's not exactly fresh blood we're sniffing here, boss.", {"entities": [[3, 22, "TIME"]]}],
["This is A.T.F. agent Ray Nicolet, Jackie Brown, Ordell Robbie money exchange trial run. It's three p.m., July 4th 1997. The location is the parking structure at LAX.", {"entities": [[34, 40, "PERSON"], [21, 32, "PERSON"], [48, 61, "PERSON"], [93, 118, "TIME"]]}],
["But you didn't seem nearly so sure in your statement to the Warren Commission.", {"entities": [[60, 77, "ORG"]]}],
["He was watching Letterman, huh? Sneaky, that Chili Palmer. So, he ever find this dry cleaner, the one with all that money on him?", {"entities": [[16, 25, "PERSON"], [45, 57, "PERSON"]]}],
["Rufus, for Christ's sake, get up.", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["It's just strange. One day someone's walking around, going to work, alive, and then...", {"entities": [[19, 26, "TIME"]]}],
["And you come into Mrs. Ryan's apartment as often as you please, looking into various health matters?", {"entities": [[23, 27, "PERSON"], [30, 39, "LOC"]]}],
["You must bring them to Mount Selaya -- on Vulcan. Only there is the passage possible. Only there can both find peace...", {"entities": [[23, 35, "GPE"]]}],
["C'mon, I'll buy you a drink.", {"entities": [[2, 5, "DATE"]]}],
["He's gay! Enrique is gay!", {"entities": [[10, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["Really, Susan, I don't think that was very proper, and besides, it's common practice now.", {"entities": [[85, 88, "TIME"], [8, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["If she identifies him. Where the fuck were you anyway, cowboy! Venza was meat. He walked right past you, and now we're the ones playing catch-up! You better hope she identifies him.", {"entities": [[109, 112, "TIME"], [63, 68, "PERSON"]]}],
["To tell you the truth, I can't believe I've made it this far. It may not be Europe, but I just know there's something special out there for me...", {"entities": [[76, 82, "GPE"]]}],
["What you did yesterday was reckless at best. You are not an employee of this hospital! If that boy dies I don't even want to think of the lawsuit that'll follow. Are we communicating here?", {"entities": [[13, 22, "DATE"], [77, 85, "LOC"]]}],
["Yes they are, Josh. Since Mankato, they have been lying eyes.", {"entities": [[26, 33, "GPE"], [14, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["So it's love which drags you to Moscow.", {"entities": [[32, 38, "GPE"]]}],
["A fine trick! Smart, aren't you? What a pack of lies you told us about those porters! Of course the minute they arrive, we can make arrangements to leave. If they take us. But you knew very well you'd tell them not to!", {"entities": [[96, 106, "TIME"]]}],
["All I'm saying is they've got people who handle these things, David. They want HBO, they'll call you.", {"entities": [[62, 67, "PERSON"], [79, 82, "ORG"]]}],
["I'm going in, Sandy. I'll see you tomorrow and tell you how it went.", {"entities": [[34, 42, "DATE"]]}],
["Mr. Data, scan the planet for lifeforms.", {"entities": [[4, 8, "PERSON"]]}],
["How about Bruce's?", {"entities": [[10, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["You know what's ridiculous? Your libretto, that's what's ridiculous. Only an idiot would ask Wolfi to work on that stuff!", {"entities": [[93, 98, "PERSON"]]}],
["God hell! I think I see the pattern! This one sounds like real trouble! You're going to need plenty of legal advice before this thing is over. As your attorney I must advise you that you'll need a very fast car with no top and after that, the cocaine. And then the tape recorder, for special music, and some Acapulco shirts... This blows my weekend, because naturally I'll have to go with you -- and we'll have to arm ourselves.", {"entities": [[308, 316, "GPE"], [338, 348, "TIME"]]}],
["I've been surprised in an unguarded hour, But must not now go back; the love that lay, Half smothered in my breast, has broke through all, Its weak restraints, and burns in its full lustre. I cannot, if I would, conceal it from thee.", {"entities": [[55, 58, "TIME"]]}],
["Freddy Newendyke.", {"entities": [[0, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["I went berserk in every battle I ever fought for King Harald...", {"entities": [[54, 60, "PERSON"]]}],
["Goddamn it Stephen!", {"entities": [[11, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now that window can never be locked. It's impossible.", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["Three years. That crime's old, man. They ain't got room in prison for all the motherfuckers out there killin' people. How they gonna find room for you?", {"entities": [[59, 65, "LOC"], [0, 11, "TIME"]]}],
["Here's your keys, Harry.", {"entities": [[18, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
["Lots of institutions. My graduate advisor believed we should experience as many environments as possible -- prisons, clinics, half-way houses. For a while I was chief therapist in a shopping mall. Had a little spot next to the yogurt place.", {"entities": [[117, 124, "LOC"], [108, 115, "LOC"], [182, 195, "LOC"]]}],
["Curt Cobain.", {"entities": [[0, 11, "PERSON"]]}],
["Upstairs and downstairs in his night gown -- He could be saying the house he's picked is two stories.", {"entities": [[68, 73, "LOC"], [31, 36, "TIME"]]}],
["Well... the crew is confined to the ship when we land at Clavius. We have to stay inside for the time it take to refit - about twenty-four hours. And then we're going to back empty.", {"entities": [[127, 144, "TIME"], [57, 64, "PERSON"]]}],
["Dr. David Ravell.", {"entities": [[4, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["Commander, Klingon vessel. Stand by to board this ship on my next signal.", {"entities": [[11, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["What could there be except just another hill? In any event, I'm not curious. At the moment, it seems to me we should be concerned about getting home. I'd give anything to be in London right now.", {"entities": [[184, 193, "TIME"], [177, 183, "GPE"]]}],
["Shit! Temp's dropping! We should have left this rock an hour ago!", {"entities": [[53, 64, "TIME"]]}],
["Mrs. Robinson, don't wreck it. I'm asking you please not to wreck it.", {"entities": [[5, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["I bet they're asleep in New York. I'll bet they're asleep all over America.", {"entities": [[67, 74, "GPE"], [24, 32, "GPE"]]}],
["I've loved you ever since I can remember, long before you married Tom Dickson.", {"entities": [[66, 77, "PERSON"]]}],
["Unfortunately, Don Colon, that is precisely where our opinions differ... Are you familiar with the work of Aristotle? Erathostene? Ptolemeus?", {"entities": [[107, 116, "PERSON"], [15, 24, "PERSON"], [131, 140, "PERSON"]]}],
["Do you ever look at those girls who work at Swenson's? They're beautiful. And I have to stand out here and watch them six nights a week.", {"entities": [[129, 135, "TIME"], [44, 51, "PERSON"], [122, 128, "TIME"]]}],
["You must be wrong, Mr. Connell, 'cause he's been marvelous about the John Doe Clubs.", {"entities": [[23, 30, "PERSON"], [69, 77, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't pimp that. You talkin' about who I think you talkin' about, you mean Rae. Rae Doole. Sexy little split tail, like you say. I can't hook you up with that. I got two girls. One ain't in town, the other one pregnant. So... you on your own.", {"entities": [[82, 91, "PERSON"], [77, 80, "PERSON"]]}],
["LaRiviere's having a hell of a time in there. Master of fucking ceremonies.", {"entities": [[0, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mr. Kringelein -- How you have changed, you look so nice.", {"entities": [[4, 14, "PERSON"]]}],
["That's part of a very interesting airline promotion giveaway that's really tremendous. I'm going to start a collection of pudding and coupons that can be redeemed for frequent flyer miles through Healthy Choice and American Airlines --", {"entities": [[215, 232, "ORG"]]}],
["Well, I want you to go to bed directly after dinner. You know how susceptible you are to colds. Harold has always been a delicate child. Even as a baby he seemed to be abnormally prone to illness - Harold, dear, eat up your beets...", {"entities": [[96, 102, "PERSON"], [39, 51, "TIME"]]}],
["In the casino.", {"entities": [[7, 13, "LOC"]]}],
["Torrio ain't like them guys. He thinks like an American. You'd like him, Charlie. He'd like you.", {"entities": [[73, 80, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mr. Rose, I'm in the *doctor* business. If you want, I can help you. You don't have to go anywhere.", {"entities": [[4, 8, "PERSON"]]}],
["I've come this far... here I am, in your house. I want you to let me pay the rent for this month. All right?", {"entities": [[86, 96, "TIME"], [41, 46, "LOC"]]}],
["It's easy. You work your way up the secret service, one day stand with the President, meet the most important people on the planet, fulfill your dreams, live happily ever after.", {"entities": [[124, 130, "LOC"], [52, 59, "TIME"]]}],
["What about the report from an eyewitness at the liquor store who said one of the brothers was shot?", {"entities": [[48, 60, "LOC"]]}],
["Evening. Welcome to Phoenix.", {"entities": [[20, 27, "GPE"], [0, 7, "TIME"]]}],
["The vintage look is over, Kat. Haven't you been reading your Sassy?", {"entities": [[26, 29, "PERSON"], [61, 66, "ORG"]]}],
["Shep, no! He gets so excited when new people are here.", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["It adds a taste of elegance for which I must confess a weakness for now and then. I call him Smedley. His real name is Frankie Jenkins - but I could hardly imagine anything more uncouth during dinner than my turning toward the kitchen and hollering ", {"entities": [[93, 100, "PERSON"], [119, 134, "PERSON"], [227, 234, "LOC"], [293, 301, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't really. But understand something- even though it may take me two or three days to sort this out- -when I'm gone, you'll still have to build the bridge. And I don't want the men to have lost respect for you.", {"entities": [[152, 158, "LOC"], [76, 86, "TIME"]]}],
["I am here representing Mr. Dumbarton, on a... matter of some delicacy.", {"entities": [[27, 36, "PERSON"]]}],
["Can't you forget for just one night that you're completely wretched?", {"entities": [[30, 35, "TIME"]]}],
["No -- Captain Charles commanded the cavalry escort, and rode outside the carriage. In the evenings, he always ate at another table. They hardly ever spoke to each other.", {"entities": [[83, 98, "TIME"], [14, 21, "PERSON"]]}],
["No, he lost the house after the stock market crash.", {"entities": [[16, 21, "LOC"]]}],
["Okay, Quellek, let's get back to the command deck and-Suddenly we hear a PISTOL BLAST and Quellek's chest turns RED. Alexander and Quellek look down at the blood, horrified.", {"entities": [[6, 13, "PERSON"], [117, 126, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't know. He went to school here, then he was in New York for awhile, then Philadelphia, and then just kind of travelling around.", {"entities": [[79, 91, "GPE"], [53, 61, "GPE"]]}],
["About six months ago, I guess it is now. God, it seems like years. What a bore! I'm embarrassed by it. Before this happened -- when I'd hear people talk about this kind of thing -- I thought it was a bunch of bullshit.", {"entities": [[6, 20, "DATE"], [36, 39, "TIME"]]}],
["Oh, Graham. No, I didn't talk to him about that. Actually, that turned out to be pretty interesting. I expected Graham to be this... well, like John, you know? I mean, he said they had gone to school together, so I was expecting lots of stories about getting drunk and secret handshakes and stuff. But he turned out to be this... this kind of character, I mean, he's kind of arty but okay, you know?", {"entities": [[4, 10, "PERSON"], [144, 148, "PERSON"]]}],
["I've got a problem, Prof. More Augus- tine than Kierkegaard, if you know what I mean. I need to know about ... demons.", {"entities": [[48, 59, "PERSON"], [26, 36, "PERSON"]]}],
["It got to you, didn't it. All the killing in the war. You need it now.", {"entities": [[66, 69, "TIME"]]}],
["Lay off, Schulz. He's got a sickness. He's krank.", {"entities": [[9, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Who's Elizabeth?", {"entities": [[6, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Jack, I don't trust you, and that's a fact. Never trust a smiling man, you can lay to that.", {"entities": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}],
["Peter, you're bleeding.", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Dunbar says you were.", {"entities": [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]}],
["This is it, Joel. It's gonna be gone soon.", {"entities": [[12, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["Talk to me, Charlie.", {"entities": [[12, 19, "PERSON"]]}],
["It will numb my wits, and I must have them all. If I'm senseless, or if I wail, then Longshanks will have broken me.", {"entities": [[85, 95, "PERSON"]]}],
["What are you doing, Herr Director?", {"entities": [[20, 24, "PERSON"]]}],
["Goddamn it, Yvonne! You don't just run away from this guy! He finds you in your dreams.", {"entities": [[12, 18, "PERSON"]]}],
["One two, Freddie's coming for you? No. Rod killed Tina. He's a fruitcake and you know it.", {"entities": [[50, 54, "PERSON"], [9, 16, "ORG"]]}],
["Before we start talking about stewardess, let's get Beaumont out of the way first.", {"entities": [[52, 60, "GPE"]]}],
["So that we could get the best price. He's got respect for you. He's gonna try to lowball me, Mike.", {"entities": [[93, 97, "PERSON"]]}],
["I think we can guarantee she'll follow us, Mr. Saavik. Remind me to explain to you the concept of human ego.", {"entities": [[47, 53, "PERSON"]]}],
["How 'bout you? Say the word and you're cold, Jack--you're dead.", {"entities": [[45, 49, "PERSON"]]}],
["Joe--what's the matter with you-- where you're concerned, I wouldn't take the slightest risk--'specially now after the great reputation you've made in the Senate. Why, look at this campaign I've started for you in all my papers. You're the logical man from the West on the National ticket--at the convention, anything can happen--", {"entities": [[0, 3, "PERSON"], [105, 108, "TIME"], [155, 161, "ORG"]]}],
["Of course not. You have all the blankets. It must be ten degrees in here. I'm telling you, Sarah, if you want to sleep with fresh air, you sleep on the fire escape. From now on that window is closed.", {"entities": [[91, 96, "PERSON"], [165, 173, "TIME"]]}],
["I really can't give out any information right now at this point.", {"entities": [[40, 49, "TIME"]]}],
["I discovered this. SEC filing... For the sale of the CBS Corporation to Westinghouse Corporation.", {"entities": [[53, 68, "ORG"], [19, 22, "ORG"], [72, 96, "ORG"]]}],
["Nothing to it, really. Claude figured they could steal a couple of bodies from the morgue. They got a couple of crackers working there don't know their asses from their elbows. Then they was gonna set fire to the infirmary and make it look like those bodies was them that got stuck inside. Claude figured during the commotion, it wouldn't be too hard to slip onto one of the fire trucks and hang tight until it rolled right on out of here in the morning.", {"entities": [[83, 89, "LOC"], [23, 29, "PERSON"], [439, 453, "TIME"]]}],
["One hundred twenty seconds to drop, bomb, have you checked your platinum euridium energy shielding?", {"entities": [[0, 26, "TIME"]]}],
["Sparazza was in failing health and looking for a donor. The son who had betrayed and burned him so thoroughly seemed a obvious choice.", {"entities": [[0, 8, "PERSON"]]}],
["No, you fucked you! Don't invert stuff! Big Tobacco tried to smear Wigand; you bought it. The Wall Street Journal, here, not exactly a bastion of anti-capitalist sentiment, refutes Big Tobacco's smear campaign as the lowest form of character assassination! And now, even now, when every word of what Wigand has said on our show is printed, the entire deposition of his testimony in a court of law in the State of Mississippi, the cat totally out of the bag, you're still standing here debating! Don, what the hell else... do you need?", {"entities": [[90, 113, "ORG"], [40, 51, "ORG"], [261, 264, "TIME"], [67, 73, "PERSON"], [404, 409, "GPE"], [413, 424, "GPE"]]}],
["This is L. B. Jefferies, a friend of Tom's. Who am I talking with?", {"entities": [[37, 40, "PERSON"], [8, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
["Oh, <u>sure</u>. Mr. Action Hero! Why couldn't I be Arnold Schwarzenegger's figment?", {"entities": [[52, 73, "PERSON"]]}],
["And that's where you met Oswald for the first time?", {"entities": [[25, 31, "PERSON"]]}],
["-- but at least Aunt May's okay now. I really have to stop by the hospital this afternoon.", {"entities": [[32, 35, "TIME"], [21, 24, "TIME"], [66, 74, "LOC"], [75, 89, "TIME"]]}],
["Awww, it's just been a shitass day. Every inch of it hot and miserable. First off, Nadine at the Blue Chip got some sorta sick, so that Mongoloid boy of hers was workin' the grill. That fuckin' idiot don't know rat shit from Rice Krispies. I ate breakfast at nine, was pukin' up pigs in a blanket like a sick dog by ten thirty.", {"entities": [[259, 263, "TIME"], [97, 106, "ORG"], [313, 326, "TIME"]]}],
["Yeah. She'll probably quit her job and stay out here with Pop. We can't leave him alone here, he'll set the damn place on fire. With Jill here a lot, it'll be good to have Margie around. Things are going to change in that department, by the way. I got a custody lawyer in Concord. I'm gonna see him tomorrow. All hell's gonna break loose, but it's worth it.", {"entities": [[272, 279, "GPE"], [133, 137, "PERSON"], [299, 307, "DATE"]]}],
["-- the bad news is there's a problem with Gordon's truck what somebody drove through the ice last night. Figured you'd know something about that, Wade.", {"entities": [[146, 150, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"], [93, 103, "TIME"]]}],
["Harry, are you going down, or you want me to?", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["The one about the Siberian bloodhound?", {"entities": [[18, 26, "GPE"]]}],
["Jesus creeping shit!", {"entities": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}],
["Again?! Jesus!", {"entities": [[8, 13, "PERSON"]]}],
["They're everywhere. Nobody's safe. And sure as hell not in the South. They like warm weather... You'd never believe it. In L.A. it's out of control. First it was drugs, now it's witchcraft.", {"entities": [[123, 127, "GPE"], [169, 172, "TIME"]]}],
["What about the money you owe me on yesterday's game?", {"entities": [[35, 44, "DATE"]]}],
["We each face death every day we're alive, Saavik.", {"entities": [[19, 28, "TIME"], [42, 48, "PERSON"]]}],
["Days... Maybe hours... Protomatter has made the situation unpredictable. I'm sorry.", {"entities": [[23, 34, "PERSON"]]}],
["All right, I will! I'll let my hair down! Why not? It can't make any real difference now. Hey Lovey, were you ever chased by the police?", {"entities": [[85, 88, "TIME"]]}],
["Right. Get me everything on Indonesia, New Guinea, all the way to Australia.", {"entities": [[39, 49, "GPE"], [28, 37, "GPE"], [66, 75, "GPE"]]}],
["Four thousand infantry and around six hundred cavalry... ... including the Green Dragoons under Tarleton.", {"entities": [[75, 89, "ORG"], [96, 104, "GPE"]]}],
["But in another twenty-four hours the core meltdown will be beyond the stabilization period. There will be no way to stop it.", {"entities": [[15, 32, "TIME"]]}],
["Nothing, only it'd be nice to spend an evening together for a change.", {"entities": [[39, 46, "TIME"]]}],
["So -- how far are we from the campus?", {"entities": [[30, 36, "LOC"]]}],
["Why should I go against you, Boss? Nobody can handle this business like you. Maranzano'll never know the crap that you forget. He's got no business bein' Boss. The idea makes me wanna puke. You're the Boss, an it's gonna stay that way.", {"entities": [[77, 86, "PERSON"]]}],
["Lots of people. Guy like Evan Twombley, Boston union official, probably got lots of people want to see him dead. The Government's been investigating his links with the Mafia.", {"entities": [[40, 46, "GPE"], [25, 38, "PERSON"]]}],
["Then give me comfort. Sleep with me tonight.", {"entities": [[36, 43, "TIME"]]}],
["Gentlemen, you notice Mr. Dickson refuses to consider our wishes. He refuses an offer to merge with the New York Trust - the only thing that will put this bank on safe ground. He insists upon running a bank on so flimsy a thing as . . . as faith!", {"entities": [[26, 33, "PERSON"], [104, 118, "ORG"]]}],
["It's going to be all right, Jake. It's going to be all right. Don't be afraid. I've got you now.", {"entities": [[28, 32, "PERSON"], [92, 95, "TIME"]]}],
["I'd rather spend the next twelve hours Outside than another five minutes in this can. This ship is bad. It watches you.", {"entities": [[60, 72, "TIME"], [21, 38, "TIME"]]}],
["Go back to the car and keep Brian there. I don't want him in here... Do it Adele... Now!", {"entities": [[28, 33, "PERSON"], [75, 80, "PERSON"], [84, 87, "TIME"]]}],
["Well Brian, I guess you can say it's arson now...", {"entities": [[43, 46, "TIME"], [5, 10, "PERSON"]]}],
["It is unfortunate that you have so few more days in Paris. Be sure and redouble your efforts so that madame can take some pleasant memories when she returns to Moscow. Good night. Good night, Leon.", {"entities": [[52, 57, "GPE"], [160, 166, "GPE"]]}],
["Well, whoever she was, Elois looked like her. So one night I walk into the club, and no Elois. Now the bartender was a wetback, he was a friend of mine, his name was Carlos. So I asked him ", {"entities": [[53, 58, "TIME"], [23, 28, "PERSON"], [95, 98, "TIME"], [147, 151, "LOC"], [166, 172, "PERSON"], [218, 225, "TIME"]]}],
["No reply, Chekov... Continue on course...", {"entities": [[10, 16, "PERSON"]]}],
["We can help you through this. Why don't you start now by telling me everything you can remember about your relationship with Clementine.", {"entities": [[50, 53, "TIME"]]}],
["Jesus Christ, Miles. Get out!", {"entities": [[0, 12, "PERSON"]]}],
["There's a little stall theatre up here. It's closed now, but I'm borrowing it for an hour. I think there's something you'd better see.", {"entities": [[82, 89, "TIME"], [52, 55, "TIME"]]}],
["Yes, yes, again, again. Do what you do to Simone. I want to know what it's like to be her just for one night.", {"entities": [[42, 48, "GPE"], [103, 108, "TIME"]]}],
["Backup man from the East Bay. Worked with Ganz a few years ago and sprung him from the road gang.", {"entities": [[20, 28, "GPE"], [42, 46, "ORG"], [47, 62, "DATE"]]}],
["They came up, made the same offer they made you folks. Our little brother Jim tried to chase 'em off, one of those detectives hit him in the head, knocked him out. Cole lost his temper.", {"entities": [[164, 168, "PERSON"], [74, 77, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mr. Rothstein, Can I be frank? You're a gambler, and I know you've had losses. I also know you could sell to Maranzano or Masseria for fifty G's, but nobody sells to those guys once. So if ya really got another buyer, and ya wanna welch, I ain't gonna beef.", {"entities": [[122, 130, "PERSON"], [4, 13, "PERSON"], [109, 118, "PERSON"]]}],
["Mr. Sim I want you to return to Dr. Bright's. I believe she is hiding something of ours there.", {"entities": [[36, 42, "PERSON"], [4, 9, "PERSON"]]}],
["It's one of the boys from headquarters. He always sings ", {"entities": [[26, 38, "LOC"]]}],
["Will you call me later to talk about asking Walter for the shrink? And we can talk about - he said you have this crying problem or something?", {"entities": [[44, 50, "PERSON"]]}],
["I am to take command of Major General Lafayette's division and lead the attack.", {"entities": [[38, 47, "PERSON"]]}],
["That's what the newspapers thought. She spent the rest of her life in the asylum. After Krueger's trial she flipped out and hung herself, so they thought.", {"entities": [[88, 95, "PERSON"]]}],
["What's going on, Tom? What happened?", {"entities": [[17, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["In my house, you watch that lip...", {"entities": [[6, 11, "LOC"]]}],
["Five minutes, Suzette, come back in five minutes. I'll ring.", {"entities": [[14, 21, "PERSON"], [0, 12, "TIME"], [33, 48, "TIME"]]}],
["Think of the fun we can have - we'll sneak down the back stairs and get in the valet's Ford. How's that?", {"entities": [[87, 91, "ORG"]]}],
["Yes. Why did you kill Debi Rutlege?", {"entities": [[22, 34, "PERSON"]]}],
["Just for a minute then.", {"entities": [[9, 17, "TIME"]]}],
["Exactly. And then -- maybe -- not right away -- There's a room right off the bedroom -- It would be perfect for a nursery. It's a walk in humidor right now -- but if I took out the refrigeration unit --", {"entities": [[77, 84, "LOC"], [58, 62, "LOC"], [146, 155, "TIME"]]}],
["Now, who are all these people?", {"entities": [[0, 3, "TIME"]]}],
["When I said before that I hoped it wasn't the end of the evening, I was, you know... talking about breakfast and stuff.", {"entities": [[57, 64, "TIME"]]}],
["IT'S NOT ABOUT GAS MONEY!! You have a thing for an actor on a stupid white soap opera, and we searched all over town for his character! Not the actor -- whose name is George, by the way. His character!", {"entities": [[167, 173, "PERSON"]]}],
["I carried that rifle in World War I. This book is a 16th Century policy report for the King of Austria. The diploma is my con- ference of degree in Latin from Trinity College. Class of 1672. It goes on.", {"entities": [[159, 174, "ORG"], [52, 64, "TIME"], [185, 189, "TIME"]]}],
["Oh, quiet, quiet, quiet. Say, tell me something did you read that speech you're gonna make tonight?", {"entities": [[91, 98, "TIME"]]}],
["I know that. Knew it when I saw you out there. The best salesman here, which isn't saying much. Want to talk to you, Dillon.", {"entities": [[117, 123, "PERSON"]]}],
["I don't know what it is about today, but I FEEL GREAT!", {"entities": [[30, 35, "DATE"]]}],
["Brian I want him out of our car!", {"entities": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}],
["Now let's see ... Eton, Cambridge ... research into robotics and plastics. Overtaken by Peter's work on the physics of climate change ...", {"entities": [[24, 33, "GPE"], [0, 3, "TIME"], [88, 93, "PERSON"]]}],
["Gettysburg's an hour's drive at most. You should be back by nightfall.", {"entities": [[13, 20, "TIME"]]}],
["This morning at Seymour's garage sale.", {"entities": [[0, 12, "TIME"], [16, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
["Is it summer or winter, Erik?", {"entities": [[6, 12, "TIME"], [16, 22, "TIME"]]}],
["We've spent everything on these operations. Is it really worth it? We've pawned your mother's wedding ring. The kids have no winter clothes...", {"entities": [[125, 131, "TIME"]]}],
["Nothing on Hannah?", {"entities": [[11, 17, "PERSON"]]}],
["I know every child is special in their own way, but Tommy sounds like a punk. I thought the play was excellent. Better than Cats.", {"entities": [[52, 57, "PERSON"]]}],
["Well, now there's something worth dying for. What do you think?", {"entities": [[6, 9, "TIME"]]}],
["She's in the bathroom.", {"entities": [[13, 21, "LOC"]]}],
["Shut it, man. Shut it. Tom is a square. He don't but dabble in shit. Maxie had me hook up a loan-back with him, through an Austrian passbook account.", {"entities": [[23, 26, "PERSON"], [69, 74, "PERSON"]]}],
["Oh, I did have a date with you tonight, didn't I?", {"entities": [[31, 38, "TIME"]]}],
["And before 1900, when people first starting swimming for recreation, before public bathing and resorts, there were very few shark attacks, cause sharks didn't know what they were missing?", {"entities": [[95, 102, "LOC"], [4, 15, "TIME"]]}],
["I never laid a hand on her in anger. Not a day. Not even when I's drinkin'. But this business got me wonderin' what a good shake and slap would do for her.", {"entities": [[41, 46, "TIME"]]}],
["Then don't come sneakin' around a man's camp.", {"entities": [[40, 44, "LOC"]]}],
["I've always liked the format of Rowan and Martin's ", {"entities": [[42, 48, "PERSON"]]}],
["I'm paying attention. I just want to look at it for a minute.", {"entities": [[52, 60, "TIME"]]}],
["Somewhere in Utah.", {"entities": [[13, 17, "GPE"]]}],
["I'm sick of watching Camp 12 win the championship. Every year they get to roast the victory pig and we get dick. This year I want that pig.", {"entities": [[113, 122, "TIME"], [51, 61, "TIME"]]}],
["Facts, Dr. Nebbleman. Facts. You've been using cryogenics to control the waste from the mouse experiment, haven't you?", {"entities": [[11, 20, "PERSON"]]}],
["So you live in Chicago now?", {"entities": [[15, 22, "GPE"], [23, 26, "TIME"]]}],
["No. I don't think you do. The other day, when he came to the cottage, he talked about a lot of things, but Danny Witwer, the man he was supposed to have just killed? He didn't mention him. He didn't say his name even once.", {"entities": [[107, 119, "PERSON"], [61, 68, "LOC"]]}],
["Mr. Kirkland has asked me to inform you that he has obtained legal representation elsewhere, and that if you have a message for him to leave it with me.", {"entities": [[4, 12, "PERSON"]]}],
["Not to worry. No signs of pathology in Nancy's EEG or pulse rate. I'd guess what we've got is a normal young girl who just happens to have gone through two days of hell.", {"entities": [[39, 44, "PERSON"], [152, 160, "TIME"]]}],
["Thank you, Anna. I'll dry it up here when I wash it next. I should hate to see our country endangered by my underwear.", {"entities": [[11, 15, "PERSON"]]}],
["Naw. You're alone in this world no matter what kinda folks or background you had. Nothing hurts, pard, once you got that one down.", {"entities": [[0, 3, "GPE"]]}],
["What? That he knew Johnny Roselli? Hoover knew a lot of gangsters.", {"entities": [[19, 33, "PERSON"], [35, 41, "PERSON"]]}],
["I'm sure of this. But not of you. You won't open any joint. I've been watching you change. You're mad now and you think you can change back. But you can't. You'll end up making beds in a boarding house.", {"entities": [[187, 201, "LOC"], [102, 105, "TIME"]]}],
["I just, I just can't believe it. I'm Minnesota's American Teen Princess!", {"entities": [[37, 46, "GPE"]]}],
["Don't do anything. Paul, I know what you're talking about.", {"entities": [[19, 23, "PERSON"]]}],
